pewterreport.com 2013-05-23

# Privacy Policy-Pewter Report: Your source for inside and breaking news on the Tampa Bay Buccaneers

This privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") applies to this website (the "Website"). The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to disclose to you what information we may collect, how we may collect it, with whom we may share it, and certain other matters related to such information, including the choices you have regarding our collection of information and our use and disclosure to other parties of information we may have collected from you.

The Website is operated by Pewter Report. We have contracted with third parties.

We own the information collected via the Website and we may use it for our own purposes, including marketing. Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to information collected on the pewterreport.com website.

When this Privacy Policy uses the term "personally identifiable information" or "personal information," we mean information that identifies a particular individual, such as your full name, street address or email address. When other information, such as a favorite team or player, is associated with personal information, it also becomes personally identifiable information for the purposes of this privacy policy.

1.  Types Of Information That May Be Collected

2.  How Information May Be Collected

3.  How We Use The Information Collected

4.  With Whom The Information May Be Shared

5.  Links To Other Websites

6.  Security

7.  Chat Rooms, Forums, and Message Boards

8.  A Special Note For Parents Concerning Privacy

9.  Your Acceptance Of The Privacy Policy And Notification Of Changes To The Privacy Policy

10.  Correcting/updating personal information

11.  Your California Privacy Rights

12.  Questions About This Privacy Policy

**1.         TYPES OF INFORMATION THAT MAY BE COLLECTED**

The following are the types of information we may collect:

**_Information You Provide Us_** In the course of using the Website, we may ask you to provide us with certain information, including contact information, such as your name, mailing address, email address, phone number, or fax number; unique identifiers, such as your user ID, or user password; demographic information, such as your date of birth or age; and financial information, such as your credit card number or similar information.

**_Website Usage Information_** We may receive and store certain types of internet usage information whenever you visit the Website, such as your click-stream data and your IP address. See "IP Addresses and Click Stream Data" section below.

**_Email Communications_** When you open emails from us, we may receive a confirmation notifying us that you opened the email, if your computer supports such capabilities. We also may keep track of what emails we send you and what emails you may be receiving from our subsidiaries and affiliates. Additionally, we keep a record of what communications you have selected to receive or not to receive. If you would like to opt-out of receiving such emails, please click on the "unsubscribe" link in the email and follow the instructions.

**_Information from Other Sources_** We may receive information about you (e.g., missing street number) from other sources and add it to your personal information.

******2.           HOW INFORMATION MAY BE COLLECTED **We may collect information from you in several different areas on the Website, including but not limited to those described below:

**_Registration_** You may be asked to complete a registration form and provide personally identifiable information; you may also be asked to choose a user ID and password in order to take advantage of certain features the Website may choose to offer, such as newsletters or contests. Your decision to register is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to us and what communications you would like to receive; however, please be advised that many products and services available on the Website require registration and if you elect not to provide such information, you will not be able to take advantage of those products and services.

**_Contests or Sweepstakes_** We periodically operate contests and sweepstakes through the Website that will require registration or the submission of personal information. Your personally identifiable information may be used to contact you for winner notification, prize delivery confirmation or other related purposes (see the rules of each contest for details about how your personal information will be used, including postings to the Website).

**_Surveys or Voting_** From time-to-time we may request personally identifiable information from you in conjunction with a survey or voting poll. Participation is voluntary, and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to the Website. At times, you may have to register to vote or to take part in a survey.

**_Games_** When you register to play games on our Website, you may be asked to provide personally identifiable information.

**_Cookies_** As with many websites, the Website uses a technology called "cookies." A cookie is a collection of information that gets stored on the hard drive of your computer when browsing the Internet. These small bits of code automatically identify your browser to the Website whenever your computer is used to visit the Website. Cookies also let us know how many people visit the Website and where visitors go on the Website. In addition, cookies can let us know non-personally identifiable information, like how many times a user has been on certain pages. For registered users, cookies can make using the Website easier for you by saving information such as your passwords or preferences. By tracking how and when you use the Website, cookies help us determine which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the Website are based on data obtained from cookies. Accepting cookies allows you, among other things, to personalize your experience on the Website. Cookies may also allow the Website to present to you advertising which may be of interest to you. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, your browser should contain an option that allows you to disable or delete cookie data at any time. Some areas of the Website, however, may not provide you with a personalized experience if you have disabled the use of cookies.

**_Web Beacons and Other Tracking Technology_** The Website uses a variety of technical methods for tracking purposes, including Web beacons. Web beacons are small pieces of data that are embedded in images on the pages of web sites. We also use these technical methods to analyze the traffic patterns on the Website, such as the frequency with which our users visit various parts of the Website. These technical methods may involve the transmission of information either directly to us or to another party authorized by us to collect information on our behalf. We also use these technical methods in HTML e-mails that we send to determine whether the recipients have opened those e-mails and/or clicked on links in those e-mails. The information from use of these technical methods may be collected in a form that is personally identifiable.

**_IP Addresses and Click-Stream Data_** We may collect IP addresses and/or click-stream data. An IP address is a number associated with the service through which you access the Internet, like your ISP (Internet service provider), your company, or your university. Standing alone, your IP address is not personally identifiable. At times, we also use IP addresses for purposes of system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers and sponsors, for example regarding the frequency with which our guests visit various parts of the Website. We may combine this information with personally identifiable information we obtain from you directly on the Website or any other of our other websites, or from third parties.

Click-stream data is information collected by our computers when you request pages from the Website. Click-stream data may include such information as the page served, the time, the source of the request, the type of browser making the request, the preceding page view and other such non-personal information. When analyzed, this data helps us analyze how visitors arrive at the Website, what type of content is most popular, what type of visitors in the aggregate are interested in particular kinds of content and advertising, and the like.

**_Transaction Information_**

If you conduct a financial or other transaction with the Website, such as subscribe to a Subscription Product or other products/services offered on the Website, we will ask you to complete an order form that will request certain information from you, including contact information, demographic information and/or financial information. In some instances, we may direct you to a third party vendor site to collect this information from you directly. Even though the collection form may have the look and feel of [www.pewterreport.com](http://www.nfl.com/), please be aware you will be giving your information directly to the third party vendor, and that in some instances such third party vendor's privacy policy will govern the collection of your personal information. Please reference the privacy policies available from these pages for any privacy related concerns.

We and/or our vendor will use this information to complete the financial or other transaction that you have requested, i.e. to deliver the information, products or other services that you request or purchase, to invoice you, and in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy. For your protection, financial information is collected and stored through encrypted means.

**3\. HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED** We own the information collected on or through the Website. As applicable, the information you provide to us may be used to:

·   contact you about the Website;

·   provide you with services or information you have requested or products or services you have ordered, such as subscription plans or other products and services

·  contact you relating to your membership status;

·   confirm or fulfill an order you have made;

·   inform you of a prize you may have won;

·   monitor or improve the use of the Website;

·   customize the advertising and content you see;

·   monitor compliance with our terms and conditions of use of the Website; and

·   send you promotional material or special offers on behalf of our marketing partners and/or their respective affiliates and subsidiaries and other third parties.

**4.         WITH WHOM THE INFORMATION MAY BE SHARED** At times, as described below, we may share your personal information with others for various purposes:

·    **Agents:** We employ other businesses (e.g., NeuLion, Inc.), certain services and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, providing the Subscription Products, sending e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, Website analysis, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They may have access to personally identifiable information needed to perform their functions, but may not use or disclose it for other purposes, like sending you marketing offers about their products.

·    **Aggregate Information:** We may share aggregate information, such as demographics and Website usage statistics, with advertisers, sponsors or other organizations. When this type of information is shared, the other parties do not have access to your personally identifiable information.

·    **Opt-in to Receive Third Party Offers:** Throughout the Website you may be presented with an opportunity to receive information and/or marketing offers sent from third party(s). Opt-in opportunities will ask you if you would like your personally identifiable information to be shared with such third party(s) as necessary to receive such information or marketing offers. If you do not elect to "opt-in" to having your personally identifiable information shared, your personally identifiable information will not be shared with such third party(s). If you do choose to have your personally identifiable information shared, your personally identifiable information will be transferred to such third party(s) solely for the purpose of permitting such third party(s) to provide you with such information and marketing offers. Such third party(s) is/are not authorized by us to disclose your personally identifiable information to any other third parties. Please be advised that if you elect to provide your personally identifiable information in response to such third party(s) marketing offers or otherwise, all information you disclose to such third party(s) will be subject to the privacy policy and practices of such third party(s). We are not responsible for the privacy practices and policies of such third party(s) and, therefore, you should review the privacy practices and policies of such third party(s) prior to providing your personally identifiable information to such third party(s).

·    **Products or Services Offered in Partnership with Third-Party(s):** Certain products and/or services available on the Website are provided to you in partnership with third party(s) and may require you to disclose personally identifiable information in order to register for and access such products and/or services. Such products and/or services shall identify the third party partners at the point of registration. If you elect to register for such products and/or services your personally identifiable information will be transferred to such third party(s) and will be subject to the privacy policy and practices of such third party(s). We are not responsible for the privacy practices and policies of such third party(s) and, therefore, you should review the privacy practices and policies of such third party(s) prior to providing your personally identifiable information in connection with such products and/or services.

·    **Subsidiaries and Affiliates:** We may share your information (including, without limitation, personally identifiable information) with all members of the Pewter Report Family.

·    **Third-Party Ad Serving and Audience and Traffic Measurement Services:** We may use a third-party network advertiser to serve the advertisements on the Website or may use a traffic measurement service to analyze the traffic on the Website. Network advertisers are third parties that display advertisements based on your visits to this Website and other websites you have visited. Third-party ad serving enables us to target advertisements to you for products or websites you might be interested in. Audience and Traffic Measurement Services allow us to collect anonymous traffic and behavior information from the Website by monitoring anonymous visitor activity. Although advertisers or other companies do not have access to the Website cookies, the Website's advertisers, sponsors and/or traffic measurement services may themselves set and access their own cookies on your computer if you choose to have your cookies enabled in your browser. Cookies allow third-party advertisers to show you advertisements or content you might be interested in. Note that any images (or any other parts of a web page) served by third parties in association with third-party cookies may serve as web beacons, which enable third parties to carry out the previously described activities. Other companies' uses of their cookies are subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp) in order to learn more about the information collection practices and "opt-out" procedures of third-party ad servers we may use.

·    **Business Transfers:** In the event that all or substantially all of our assets are sold or transferred to another party, or another transaction occurs in which your personally identifiable information is one of the business assets transferred, all personally identifiable information that has been collected and saved may be one of the business assets we transfer. You will be notified of such a transfer in accordance with the "Changes to the Policy" section below.

·    **Administrative or Legal Process:** We or others may disclose your personal information to third parties without notice to you in order to comply with applicable law, law enforcement agencies, to protect our or third parties' rights, or to protect the rights of other users of the Website.

**5.         LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES** You should be aware that when you are on the Website you could be directed to other websites beyond our control. For example, if you "click" on a banner advertisement, the "click" may take you off the Website onto a different website. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors and marketing partners that may use the Website's logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other websites may send their own cookies to you, independently collect data or solicit personal information and may or may not have their own published privacy policies. If you visit a website that is linked to the Website, you should consult that website's privacy policy before providing any personal information.

**6.         SECURITY** The Website incorporates reasonable safeguards to protect the security, integrity, completeness, accuracy and privacy of the personal information that we may collect and we have put into place reasonable precautions to protect such information from loss, misuse and alteration. Your personally identifiable information is transferred to our computers utilizing encryption software. Only those employees who need access to your information in order to do their jobs are allowed access. Our security policies are reviewed periodically and revised as required.

**7.          CHAT ROOMS, FORUMS, AND MESSAGE BOARDS**

The Website may make chat rooms, forums and message boards available to you and other users. You are not required to provide any personal information when using these areas but you may choose to do so. If you post personal information online, it will be publicly available and you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties. We cannot ensure the security of any information you choose to make public in a chat room, forum, or message board. Also, we cannot ensure that parties who have access to such publicly available information will respect your privacy. Please exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these areas.

**8.          A SPECIAL NOTE FOR PARENTS CONCERNING PRIVACY** The Website is a general audience website. On the Website, we do not currently knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen. If, in the future, we collect personally identifiable information from children on the Website, we will do so in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (15 U.S.C. 6501 et seq.) including, without limitation, obtaining necessary parental consent.

The Internet offers children wonderful educational and entertainment resources. Your guidance and involvement are essential to help ensure that children have a safe and rewarding online experience. We encourage you to visit the [Direct Marketing Association's website](http://www.the-dma.org/) and explore the Get CyberSavvy! Program as well as the [GetNetWise website](http://www.getnetwise.org/) to learn more about parental control tools.

**9.         YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THE PRIVACY POLICY AND NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY** By using the Website, you signify your agreement to the terms of this Privacy Policy. We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make a material change to the way in which we collect, use, and/or share your personal information, we will post a notice on the Website and / or send an email to users who have provided an email address. We will assume that you have given your permission for your information to be used under the terms of the Privacy Policy, as modified, if you do not respond to our email within thirty days or continue to use the Website thirty days after a notice is posted. Please note that you should always update your personal information to provide us with a current email address.

**10.       CORRECTING/UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION** If your personally identifiable information changes (such as your email address or zip code), or if you no longer desire to have access to the Website, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove the personal data you have provided to us. You may request that we do so by emailing us, signing into your online account and making the desired changes, or via mail.

If you have anyquestions about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, contact Pewter Report.

**12.        QUESTIONS ABOUT THIS PRIVACY POLICY** If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the privacy practices of this Website, please contact us by email.
